A Guide to the Records of Eastern State Hospital, 1770-2009
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Buildings and Grounds Records, 1829-1996., Extent: 4.95 cu. ft; 2 volumes; 42 oversize folders. (Box 02-12;, Volume 034, 091;, Map-cabinet 9 and Super Oversize: 4.)
  - Subseries C. Building Files, 1936-1996., Extent: 4.95 cu. ft.; 1 volume. (Box 02-12;, Volume 091.)
    - Building 9, Specifications for remodel (first floor), 1968. (Box 03, Folder 6)
    - Building 9, Specifications for remodel (first floor), 1968. (Box 03, Folder 7)
    - Building 9, Specifications for remodel (first floor), 1969. (Box 03, Folder 8)
    - Building 27, Documentation of partial basement, 1971. (Box 03, Folder 9)
    - Building 27, Renovation project report (Vocational Rehabilitation), 1969-1970. (Box 03, Folder 10)
    - Building 27, Specifications for renovation of partial basement, 1970. (Box 03, Folder 11)
    - Building 27, Specifications for renovation of partial basement, 1970. (Box 03, Folder 12)
    - Building 27, Specifications for renovation of partial basement (as built), 1972. (Box 04, Folder 1)
    - Buildings 22 and 27 (Dr. Joseph E. Barrett), 1948-1952. (Box 04, Folder 2)
    - Buildings 22 and 27 (Wayne C. Clark, Clerk of the Works, Dunbar Construction), 1949-1950. (Box 04, Folder 3)
    - Buildings 22, 27, and 43 (Wiley and Wilson Construction Engineers), 1945-1949. (Box 04, Folder 4)
    - Central heathing plant auxillary equipment and piping specifications, 1936. (Box 04, Folder 5)
    - Coal storage, Concrete pad and retaining wall for, 1972-1974. (Box 04, Folder 6)
    - Continued Treatment building 29 (Joseph E. Barrett, Commissioner), 1951. (Box 04, Folder 7)
    - Continued Treatment building 30, Maintenance and operating instructions, 1962. (Box 04, Folder 8)
    - Continued Treatment buildings, Specifications for test borings, 1956-1957. (Box 04, Folder 9)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 24, 26, 29, 1956-1957. (Box 04, Folder 10)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 24, 26, 29, 1956-1957; 1975. (Box 04, Folder 11)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 24, 26, 29, Operating and maintenance instructions for air conditioning, heating, ventilating and plumbing equipment, 1959. (Box 04, Folder 12)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 24, 26, 29, Operating and maintenance instructions for air conditioning, heating, ventilating and plumbing equipment, 1959. (Box 04, Folder 13)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 24, 29, 30, List of requirements for, 1956. (Box 04, Folder 14)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 24, 29, 30, Outside utilities (Whitlock-Dunn), 1957-1961. (Box 05, Folder 1)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 25 and 28 (Baskervill and Son / Hankins and Anderson), 1954-1973. (Box 05, Folder 2)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 25 and 28 (J. Kennon Perrin Co.), 1956-1958. (Box 05, Folder 3)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 25 and 28 (Joseph E. Barrett, Commmissioner), 1954-1958. (Box 05, Folder 4)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 25 and 28, Outside utilities, 1956-1959. (Box 05, Folder 5)
    - Continued Treatment buildings 26, 29, 34, 1957-1975. (Box 05, Folder 6)
    - Education building and residence hall for student nurses, 1969-1971. (Box 05, Folder 7)
    - Education building and residence hall for student nurses, 1971-1972. (Box 05, Folder 8)
    - Education building and residence hall for student nurses, 1972. (Box 05, Folder 9)
    - Education building and residence hall for student nurses, 1972. (Box 05, Folder 10)
    - Education building and residence hall for student nurses, 1973. (Box 06, Folder 1)
    - Education building and residence hall for student nurses, 1974-1976. (Box 06, Folder 2)
    - Electric distribution system specifications (personnel building area), 1950. (Box 06, Folder 3)
    - Emergency generator specifications, 1969. (Box 06, Folder 4)
    - Fire hazards, Correction of (Downtown Site), 1955. (Box 06, Folder 5)
    - Fire protection and insurance documents, 1950. (Box 06, Folder 6)
    - Fire protection and insurance report, 1938. (Box 06, Folder 7)
    - Geriatric complex, 1963-1966. (Box 06, Folder 8)
    - Geriatric Unit, Outside utilities, 1962-1968. (Box 06, Folder 9)
    - Glass House sewage treatment plant, 1973-1976. (Box 06, Folder 10)
    - Kitchen building (#13, Baskervill and Sons / Hankins and Anderson), 1953. (Box 06, Folder 11)
    - Kitchen building (#13, Baskervill and Sons / Hankins and Anderson), 1953-1954. (Box 07, Folder 1)
    - Kitchen building (#13, Baskervill and Sons / Hankins and Anderson), 1954-1956. (Box 07, Folder 2)
    - Kitchen building (#13, Baskervill and Sons / Hankins and Anderson), 1956-1957. (Box 07, Folder 3)
    - Kitchen building (#13, Baskervill and Sons / Hankins and Anderson), 1957-1959. (Box 07, Folder 4)
    - Kitchen building (#13, Dunbar), 1954. (Box 07, Folder 5)
    - Kitchen building (#13, Dunbar), 1954-1955. (Box 07, Folder 6)
    - Kitchen building, Outside utilities, 1954. (Box 07, Folder 7)
    - Kitchen / Cafeteria equipment, 1957-1958. (Box 08, Folder 1)
    - Kitchen / Cafeteria equipment, 1957-1958. (Box 08, Folder 2)
    - Kitchen / Cafeteria equipment, 1957-1958. (Box 08, Folder 3)
    - Kitchen / Cafeteria equipment, 1957-1958. (Box 08, Folder 4)
    - Kitchen / Cafeteria equipment, Utility connections, 1958-1959. (Box 08, Folder 5)
    - Laundry building (#17, Baskervill and Sons / Hankins and Anderson), 1953. (Box 08, Folder 6)
    - Laundry building (#17, Joseph E. Barrett, Commissioner), 1953-1954. (Box 08, Folder 7)
    - Laundry building (#17, Southern Engineering and Construction Company), 1953-1955. (Box 08, Folder 8)
    - Laundry building, Renovation of (#17, operation and maintenance manual), 1983; undated. (Box 08, Folder 9)
    - Longhill connector road, 1984-1989. (Box 09, Folder 1)
    - Medical-Surgical building, 1969-1970. (Box 09, Folder 2)
    - Medical-Surgical building, 1970-1972. (Box 09, Folder 3)
    - Medical-Surgical building, Appraisal of, 1970. (Box 09, Folder 4)
    - Occupational Therapy and Recreation building, Outside utilities for, 1963. (Box 09, Folder 5)
    - Occupational Therapy and Recreation building, Outside utilities for, 1963. (Box 09, Folder 6)
    - Occupational Therapy and Recreation building, Outside utilities for (addendum), 1963. (Box 09, Folder 7)
    - Occupational Therapy and Recreation building, Report on preliminary design for outside utilities, 1963. (Box 09, Folder 8)
    - Outside utilities, Report on preliminary design (buildings 1, 2, 24, 26, 29), 1958. (Box 09, Folder 9)
    - Outside utilities, Report on preliminary design (buildings 9, 10, 11, 12, 30), 1960. (Box 09, Folder 10)
    - Overhead electric and telephone, Location of circuits (outside utilities for buildings 9, 10, 11, 12, 30), 1961. (Box 09, Folder 11)
    - Picnic and recreation area, 1958-1964. (Box 09, Folder 12)
    - Playground area for building 22, 1961. (Box 09, Folder 13)
    - Playground fence specifications, 1958. (Box 09, Folder 14)
    - Radial brick chimney specifications, 1948-1951. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Radial brick chimney specifications, 1951. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Railroad trestle / coal pit, 1957-1976. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Railroad trestle / coal pit, 1976-1978. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Railroad trestle / coal pit, 1979-1993. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Receiving building, 1955-1959. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Receiving building, 1959. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Receiving building, 1959. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Receiving building, 1959-1976. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Receiving building, Waterproofing basement of, 1969-1971. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Recreation Center, Specifications for construction, utilities and grading for, 1964. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Route 199, 1986-1996. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Sanitary sewer lines and sewage treatment plant specifications, 1951. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Stoker and control equipment (addendum #1 to specifications), 1950. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Storage and maintenance shops building, 1965-1967. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Storage and maintenance shops building, 1967-1975. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Storeroom and maintenance shop building, 1964-1970. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Storeroom and maintenance shop building, 1970-1972. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Storm sewers (addendum #1 to specifications), 1950. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Water distribution system specifications, 1951. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Water distribution system specifications (addendum #1), 1951. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Water storage tank and tower, Contract for (Dunbar), 1936. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Water supply, Development of, 1943-1966. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Water supply, Development of, 1966-1967. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Water supply improvements, Report of permanent, 1944. (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Series III. Commitment Registers, 1911-1946., Extent: 2 volumes. (Volume 035-036.)
  Restricted: commitment registers that are less than 125 years old. Due to the presence of restricted patient information, these records may require review by an archivist and/or redaction (if it is possible) before they are served. Commitment registers include the date upon which patient applications were received, the name of each patient, the name of the sheriff or police officer reporting the commitment, the place of residence of the patient, and the date of admission, if the patient was admitted. The volumes may also include reasons for rejection, notations concerning escapes, deaths, and whether the patient was picked up from the local jail. Researchers should also note that sporadic early commitment papers can be found in Series IV., Subseries D. Correspondence, Subject Files and Ledgers (Superintendent).
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Applications received / Commitments, Record of, 1911-1928. (Volume 035)
  - Commitment papers received, Register of, 1935-1946. (Volume 036)
- Series IV. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1791-1997., Extent: 9.125 cu. ft., 3 volumes. (Box 13-33., Volume 037-039.)
  Contains correspondence and subject files maintained by Eastern State Hospital administrators, directors, and superintendents. The files document the administrative and operational aspects of the hospital, as well as legislation, public health issues, and special programs. The earliest files also contain patient-related correspondence, essays on medical topics, and reports.
  This series contains four subseries that are divided according to the office or person responsible for creating and/or maintaining the records. The division between records of the director and records of the superintendent is fluid and dates may overlap.
  - Subseries A. Correspondence and Subject Files (Assistant Director, Administrative), 1954-1997., Extent: .45 cu. ft. (Box 13.)
    Correspondence and miscellaneous subject files created and/or maintained by the Assistant Director, Administrative, Martin S. Kline. Files include those related to the history of the institution, loan agreements, and medical records automation.
    Arranged alphabetically according to folder title.
    - Eastern State Hospital, History of, 1954-1996. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Eastern State Hospital Retirees Association, History of, 1989. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Grand master key, 1978-1985. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - HJR 240 Joint Subcommittee, 1996-1997. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - HJR 240 Joint Subcommittee, 1996-1997. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Loan agreements, Colonial Williamsburg, 1983-1984. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Patient Resident Automated Information System (PRAIS), 1988-1992. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Patient Resident Automated Information System (PRAIS), 1988-1992. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Peninsulas Emergency Medical Services Council, 1996. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Portrait of Dr. Joseph E. Barrett, Conservation of the, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Unclaimed property, Sale of, 1980-1982. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Unclaimed property, Sale of, 1980-1982. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Visions, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Subseries B. Correspondence and Subject Files (Director), 1937-1993., Extent: 4.95 cu. ft. (Box 14-24.)
    Restricted: records containing patient names or information that are less than 125 years old. Some records may require review by an archivist and/or redaction (if it is possible) before they are served. These items have been flagged.
    Correspondence and miscellaneous subject files from various/unknown offices, most likely the Office of the Director. Topics of interest include the Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, patient population statistical reports and surveys, the hospital's compliance with the Civil Rights Act, and the Child and Adolescent program. The files cover the administrations of several hospital directors, including Dr. Granville L. Jones, Dr. Joseph E. Barrett, Dr. Kurt T. Schmidt, and David Pribble.
    - 200th Anniversary program, 1973. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 200th Anniversary, Southeastern Divisional Meeting of the American Psychiatric Association (drawings of Eastern State Hospital), 1973. (Box 02)
    - 300th Anniversary Walk: The Public Hospital, 1999. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Admissions Unit, Establishment of, 1980-1982. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Admissions Unit, Establishment of, 1982-1983. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Adolescent Inpatient Services (possible transfer to Central State Hospital), 1982-1983. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - American Hospital Association surveys and questionnaires, 1944-1956. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - American Hospital Association surveys and questionnaires, 1957-1962. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - American Hospital Association surveys and questionnaires, 1963-1967. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - American Hospital Association surveys and questionnaires, 1968-1972. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - American Hospital Association surveys and questionnaires, 1973-1980. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - American Hospital Association surveys and questionnaires, 1981-1986. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - American Hospital Association surveys and questionnaires, 1987-1991. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - American Medical Association surveys and questionnaires, 1937-1956. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Ashbury, Howard H., M.D.: Biographical information, 1961-1971. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Barbara Dike Memorial Staff Library, 1986. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Brochures, undated. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Budget requests (1946-1948), Notes concerning, undated. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Building dedication: Henry E. Davis Building, 1964. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Building dedications: Brown Building and Caldwell Building, 1969. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Caldwell, Lawrence, 1968-1986. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Capital outlay study (general statement), 1960. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Cattle records, 1922-1942. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Cemetery and incinerator records, 1946. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Child and Adolescent Program, 1976-1978. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Child and Adolescent Program, 1978-1982. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Child and Adolescent Program, 1983-1989. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Child and Adolescent Program, 1989-1992. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Child and Adolescent Program closure, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Child and Adolescent Program closure, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Children's Unit historical information, 1983. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Chronology of special events, 1967-1982. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights Act, Compliance with, 1964-1966. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights Act, Compliance with, 1967-1972. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights Act, Compliance with, 1973-1982. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Classification of resident patients and lists of ward personnel, 1955. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Commission on Economic State Government (Senate Resolution 53), Report to the, 1960. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Confidentiality policy, 1981. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Ashbury, Howard H., M.D. (Superintendent), 1960-1969. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Jones, Granville L., M.D. (Superintendent), 1948-1956. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Pribble, David C. (Director), 1981-1991. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence to: Ruth, Alfred E.H., (Director, Division of Mental Hospitals), 1956-1968. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with: Morel, Louise C., (great-great grandaughter of Dr. John M. Galt), 1956-1968. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Counties and cities served by Eastern State Hospital (1950 census), undated; circa 1953. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Criteria for admission, 1981. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Demolition of buildings, 1984. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commissioner: Allerton, Dr. William S., 1970-1976. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commissioner: Bevilacqua, Dr. Joseph J., 1981-1983. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commissioner: Bevilacqua, Dr. Joseph J., 1984-1985. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commissioner: Bevilacqua, Dr. Joseph J., 1985. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commissioner: Cullum, Howard M., 1982-1985. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commissioner: Cullum, Howard M., 1986. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commissioner: Kirven, Leo E., Jr., M.D., 1977-1979. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Commissioner: Kirven, Leo E., Jr., M.D., 1980-1981. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Deputy Commissioner: Funkhouser, James B., 1958-1979. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Commissioner: Cullum, Howard M., 1987. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Commissioner: Cullum, Howard M., 1988-1990. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Commissioner: Davis, Dr. King E., 1990. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Commissioner: Davis, Dr. King E., 1991-1992. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Commissioner: Davis, Dr. King E., 1993-1994. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Commissioner: Davis, Dr. King E., Executive Forum Subcommittee, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Subtance Abuse Services, Deputy Commissioner: Fidura, Jennifer G., 1986-1990. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1973-1974. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1975-1976. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1977-1979. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1980-1981. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1982. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1983. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1984-1985. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1986-1990. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Dept. of Mental Hygiene and Hospitals, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1962-1969. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Mental Hygiene and Hospitals, Information Director/Press Secretary, 1970-1972. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Directors of Eastern State Hospital, List of (1773-1972), undated. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Discharge planning memorandum, 1981. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Dunbar building 8, 1962. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, 1965-1967. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, 1968-1969. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, 1969-1970. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, 1970. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, 1970-1971. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, 1971. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, 1971. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Eastern State Hospital Bicentennial Anniversary Commission, 1972-1973. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Estimates for new construction and capital outlay projects to complete approved site plan (Dunbar site), 1954. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Exhibit loan agreements, Virginia Historical Society, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Facility accomplishments (1984-1886 biennium), 1987. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Food service operations, 1984-1987. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Functional unit and program descriptions, 1983-1984. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Galt book collection, undated. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Galt Mental Health Scholar, 1982-1992. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Guest book, 1956-1961. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Haldol controversy (FDA), 1973. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Historical records (memoranda), 1982-1993. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Holiday message/card, 1981. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Hospital/community meeting, 1981. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Information for relatives (written by Granville L. Jones, M.D.), 1949. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Jamestown 350th Anniversary Commission, 1955-1956. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Jamestown 350th Anniversary Commission, 1956-1957. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Jamestown 350th Anniversary Commission, 1957-1958. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Letter from former patient, 1973. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Letter to Dr. Barrett from Mary Meares Galt about Dr. John M. Galt, II. (photocopy), 1963. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Loan of museum artifacts to Science Museum, 1978-1979. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Map of Dunbar site (with legend), undated. (Box 02)
    - Memoranda (miscellaneous), 1953-1972. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Mental Health Day at Eastern State Hospital (programs), 1956-1958. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Mental Health Week-National Rally Against Mental Illness (program), 1963. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Monthly reports to the Assistant Commissioner, 1981. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Muscarelle Museum of Art Galt exhibit, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Organizational charts, 1976. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Overcrowding, 1971. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Patient handbooks, 1980-1981. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Patient movement and census statistics, 1945-1956. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Patient movement and census statistics, 1959-1960. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Patient population report and statistics (submitted to the Bureau of the Census), 1937. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Patient population report and statistics (submitted to the Bureau of the Census), 1944. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Patient population report and statistics (submitted to the Bureau of the Census), 1945. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Patient population report and statistics (submitted to the National Institute of Health), 1952. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Patient population report and statistics (submitted to the Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare), 1960. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Patient population survey, 1960. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Patients over 50 years of age (statistics), 1951. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Photo album, unidentified (photocopy), undated. (Box 21, Folder 19)